<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="epb_heading_preparation">Preparation</string>

    <string name="epb_introduction_heading">Introduction</string>
    <string name="epb_introduction_text">
        We have come together in our Father&apos;s presence to offer him,
        through our Lord Jesus Christ, praise and thanksgiving; to
        hear his most holy Word; to pray for others as well as ourselves;
        and to ask forgiveness for our sins. Let us then confess our
        sins to Almighty God and pray together:
    </string>

    <string name="epb_confession_heading">Confession &amp; Absolution</string>
    <string-array name="epb_confession_texts">
        <item>
            Almighty and most merciful Father,\n
            we have erred and strayed from your ways like lost sheep.\n
            We have followed too much \n
            the devices and desires of our own hearts;\n
            we have broken your holy laws;\n
            we have left undone what we ought to have done,\n
            and we have done what we ought not to have done.\n
            O Lord, have mercy on us pitiful sinners.\n
            Spare those, O God, who confess their faults.\n
            Restore those who truly repent,\n
            as you have promised through Jesus Christ our Lord.\n
            And grant, O merciful Father, for his sake,\n
            that we may live a godly, righteous, and disciplined life,\n
            to the praise of your holy name. Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            Most merciful Father, our Creator and Judge,\n
            we acknowledge and confess that we have sinned against you\n
            in thought, word, and deed.\m
            We have not loved you with all our heart;\n
            and we have not loved our neighbours as ourselves.\n
            We earnestly repent, and are truly sorry for all our sins.\n
            For your Son our Lord Jesus Christ's sake forgive us,\n
            and strengthen us to serve and obey you\n
            in lives wholly renewed by your Spirit;\n
            through Jesus Christ our Lord.  Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>